Guide to the Hadley Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional material, 1729-1950; Accession 2013-M-043; 2.25; (5 boxes)
  - Arthur Twining Hadley correspondence, with notes
    - 1890, circa 1940 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - 1891, 1937-1940 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - 1892, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - 1893, circa 1940 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - 1894, circa 1940 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - 1895 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 1896 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 1897 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 1898, circa 1940 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 1899, 1937-1940 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 1900, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 1902 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 1903, circa 1940 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 1904 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - 1905, circa 1940 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - 1906, circa 1940 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - 1907, circa 1940 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - 1908, circa 1940 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 1909, circa 1940 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - 1910, circa 1940 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 1911-1912, circa 1940 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - 1912, circa 1940 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 1913, circa 1940 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - 1914, 1934-1941 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 1915, circa 1940 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 1916, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 1917, circa 1941 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - 1918, circa 1940 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 1919, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - "19-B", Yale reorganization, 1919-1920 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - 1920, circa 1940 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - 1921, circa 1940 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - 1922, circa 1940 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 1923, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - 1924, circa 1940 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 1925 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - 1926, circa 1940 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 1927, circa 1940 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - 1928, circa 1940 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - 1929, circa 1940 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 1930, circa 1940 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Letters, not needed for book (in order), 1884-1897, circa 1929 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - After March 5, 1930, 1930-1946 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Letters of no use for book, but too good to throw away, Circa 1876-1899 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Parents and family (ATH book), 1864, 1891-1894, 1919 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Letters of interest (only) because from celebrities, 1870-1938 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Materials related to Morris Hadley's biography of Arthur Twining Hadley
    - Correspondence, 1934-1948 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Book I, Outline, Circa 1940-1948 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Book II, Sources, 1932-1946 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Book III, Work sheets, Circa 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Book IV, Bibliography, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Book X, Circa 1940 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Book XI [Chapter I], Circa 1940 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Book XII [Chapter II], Circa 1942 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Book XIII [Chapter III], 1941 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Book XIV [Chapter IV], 1942 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Book XV [ Chapter V], 1942 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Book XVI [Chapter V, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Book XVII [Chapter VII], 1942 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Book XVIII [Chapter VIII], 1942-1946 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Book XIX [Chapter IX], 1942-1946 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Book XX [Chapter X], 1946 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Book XXI [Chapter XI], 1946 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Book XXII [Chapter XII], War and reconstruction, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Book XXIII [Chapter XIII], Retrospect, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Book XXIV [Chapter XIV], Active retirement, 1946-1947 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Articles about ATH, 1914-1946 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Material related to the publication of James Hadley's diary
    - James Hadley manuscripts and notes by Morris Hadley, Circa 1843, 1943, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - James Hadley diary
      - Notes, 1940-1948 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1941-1950 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - James Hadley -- Life, 1901-1904 (Box 5, Folder 7)